





Summary

Jump to Section

Adocumentation specialist with over 11 years of experience in the IT industry. Tasked with designing and developing various product documentation, blogs, training videos, learning materials and program plans, while working closely with managers, business analysts, product teams as well as clients.

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Work Experience

C3M LLC as Senior Technical Writer May 2019 to Till Date

C3MLLC (https://www.c3m.io) is a startup with a unique platform that handles cloud security and compliance, helping organizations gain complete visibility into their security posture and constantly enforce security best practices.

Responsibilities:

Single-handedly prepare end user documentation for CLOUD CONTROL (cloud security and compliance platform, developed by C3M).

Develop user documentation templates as per the requirements.

Identify modules and screens in scope for the project.

Estimate effort, and timeline for the project.

Write blogs on Cloud security, compliance standards, cloud monitoring, secure cloud architecture etc.

Identify the relevant topics for blogs, research and generate content to be added to company website as well as other channels

Blogs written : https://www.c3m.io/resources/

Creating Write-ups, mailers, flyers with regards to product features.

Coordinate with the development as well as business teams to obtain a clearer picture on the feature and create documents by the committed release dates.

Freelancer as Freelance Writer Sep 2018 to May 2019

IBS Software Services Pvt. Ltd., as Associate Consultant & Senior Product Trainer Jul 2008 to Jul 2018

Associated with IBS Software Services Pvt. Ltd., Kochi. (July 2008 - July 2018) As an Associate Consultant & Senior Product Trainer from 2014 to 2018. As a Senior Technical Writer & Product Trainer from 2011 to 2014. As a Technical Writer from 2008 to 2011.

IBS Software Services Pvt. Ltd. (www.ibsplc.com) is a leading global provider of new generation IT solutions to the Travel, Transportation and Logistics industries.

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld เของคดแจเกแแดง

Single-handedly prepare end user documentation for iFly Res (a passenger reservation system, developed by IBS).

Coordinate and communicate with multiple teams of Business Analysts handling multiple modules of the application, getting required inputs creating documents by the committed dates of delivery.

Function as a lead for documentation by planning, tracking and reporting status for various documentation initiatives.

Develop user documentation templates as per the project requirements.

Identify modules and screens in scope for the project.

Estimate effort, resources and timeline for the project.

Assign and track documentation activities.

Arrange and handle training for team members.

Thoroughly study the business and develop documentation based on standard template.

Ensure quality of the documentation.

Coordinate with SMEs and business analysts for training sessions and reviews.

Provide management with status reports on progress of work.

Deliver documentation as per agreement.

Collect and analyze feedback on documents delivered.

Help product team with research and information gathering and proof-reading the draft to fine-tune the document.

Act as mentor to junior members in the team.

Maintaining client satisfaction through effective and timely communication and schedule adherence.

Work together with clients, to understand the scope of training required and plan training for the client personnel based on their role as well as requirements.

Conduct End User Trainer programs at client sites, our offices as well as over WebEx

Conduct and support the Train the Trainer programs at client sites.

Regularly coordinate and handle the induction training for new joiners as well as laterals joining the organization.

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from MAHATMA GANDHI UNIVERSITY, KOTTAYAM in 2007

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name JIRA	Version Last Used	Experience
MICROSOFT OFFICE SUITE		
Google Suite		
Adobe professional		
Adobe Frame maker		
Freshdesk, Gitbook, Confluence		

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Malayalam				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.